zerbee.com 2019-09-28

# Privacy Policy - Zerbee

**What information do we collect?**  

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information (ordering only). You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- To process transactions

\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

\- To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.  We will also send periodic promotional emails featuring coupons and special offers.  At any time you may “opt out” or unsubscribe from our promotional emails by clicking the unsubscribe links in the email you received.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to another company other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  We may transfer your personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, aquisition, dissolution or similar event.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your payment information will not be kept on file for more than 14 days.

**Do we use cookies?**  

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California** **Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**  

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.zerbee.com](http://www.zerbee.com/)

**Your Consent**  

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy as well as our terms and conditions.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**  

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Zerbee, LLC  
6645 James Avenue North  
Minneapolis, MN 55430  
USA  
privacy@zerbee.com
